omgili.com 2013-11-09

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: July 14th, 2009

## Omgili Privacy Policy

Omgili does not currently collect personally identifiable information regarding its users and visitors to its Website.  
Omgili may however collect certain other information regarding its users and visitors to its Website. This information may include:  

  * Information supplied by the users' browsers when accessing the Website and/or "Omgili Buzz Graphs", such as IP address, type of browser, date and time of access, etc.;
  * Search terms; and
  * Parameters selected by users to define the information provided by "Omgili Buzz Graphs".

This Privacy Policy sets forth the uses Omgili may make of such information, measures that Omgili takes to protect such information and the circumstances under which it may disclose such information. By using the Website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  
As used in this Privacy Policy:  

  * " **Services** " means the services provided by the Website, including the "Omgili Buzz Graphs";
  * " **Website** " means the omgili.com domain and any sub-domains thereof;
  * " **Omgili** " means Omgili Ltd. and any of its subsidiaries.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time including for purposes of adapting it to new features offered by Omgili, therefore Omgili asks you to check back periodically. If in the future Omgili will collect personally identifiable information from its users and visitors to its Website, it will update the terms of this Privacy Policy to include appropriate terms for the use and disclosure of personally identifiable information.  

### Uses of Information

Omgili uses the information it collects for the following purposes:  

  * _Internal Use and Diagnostics_. Omgili uses the information collected for internal purposes, to improve its Website and Services, and to better tailor the Website and Services to meet your needs. This may include compiling user diagnostics based on geographical locations, search terms requested and/or defined parameters for "Omgili Buzz Graphs".
  * _Resolving Problems_. Omgili may use information and other data it obtains from your current and past activities to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems and to monitor and enforce the Omgili Terms of Use.

### Disclosure of Information

Omgili may disclose the information it collects in the following circumstances: 

  * _Merger or Sale_. In the event that Omgili merges with or is acquired by another business entity or sells all or substantially all of its assets to an acquirer, Omgili may share some or all of the information it collects with the merged or acquiring company in order to continue serving you and others and continuing to offer you the Services.
  * _Special Cases_. In the event that Omgili has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Omgili's Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Omgili's rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. In addition, Omgili may disclose information in the event that Omgili believes in good faith that the law requires such disclosure or if it is ordered to do so by a court.
  * _Business Partners and Investors_. In the event that Omgili adds business partners or co-branded sites to its Website or is involved in discussions with potential investors, provided that the sharing of information with such business partners and investors will be limited to statistical information regarding users in general. 
  * _PR Purposes: In the event Omgili wishes to publicize information for PR purposes_ , provided that such sharing of information will be limited only to statistical information regarding users in general.

_Links and Displayed Sites_. The Website may contain links to other sites. Omgili is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such linked or otherwise displayed sites. 

### Security

Omgili has put in place on the Website reasonable security measures to protect the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of the user information that it collects. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Omgili strives to protect the user information it collects, Omgili cannot ensure the security of any such information. 

### Cookies

You acknowledge and agree that Omgili may use cookies on the Website. A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your hard drive and can store information about your use of the Services. Omgili uses cookies for website analytic purposes. You can delete cookies from your computer at your sole discretion. 

### Third Party Advertisers

Omgili uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this Website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

### Google AdSense

We participate in Google AdSense (www.google.com/adsense) and use Google to stream advertisements to our site. The content of the AdSense advertisements on our Website is posted by Google and not by Omgili. Google may collect certain information regarding visitors to our site via the AdSense advertisements and may place cookies on your computer. To learn more about Google's policy regarding maintaining the privacy of such information that it collects, please visit www.google.com/privacy.html. 

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Omgili, or any related issues, Omgili will be pleased to assist you. You may contact Omgili at info@omgili.com. 

### Subordination to the User Agreement

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of Omgili's Terms of Use located at <http://omgili.com/tos.html> as an integral part thereof; in case of a contradiction between any provision of the Terms of Use and the content of this document, the provisions of the Terms of Use shall prevail.
